actionsprout.io 2019-02-28

# ActionSprout Privacy Policy | ActionSprout Help Center

This privacy statement describes how we collect and use the personal information you provide on our site. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

#### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

#### The Information We Collect and How We Use It

In order to provide services to you, we may collect the following types of information:

**Information you provide** : When you participate in an ActionSprout campaign we will store and save the information you provide or authorize Facebook to provide. This information may include personally identifiable information such as your name, postal address, email address, etc.

**Cookies** : When you access files on the website, one or more cookies will be sent and stored on your computer. These cookies are used to save certain preferences on the website and identify you on future visits.

**Log information** : All information sent by your web browser and computer when you visit the website may be stored by our servers. This information may include your IP address, browser type, URL accessed, cookie information, the date and time of your request, and other information that may uniquely identify you.

#### Choices For Personal Information

You can choose to limit the storage of cookies on your computer when accessing the website. Limiting or prohibiting cookies from being stored on your computer may affect the usability of the website services.

#### Information Sharing

Information collected about you may be shared with third parties to facilitate the serving of advertising on the website. Some of these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) may use technology such as cookies and web beacons and may collect additional information about you.

ActionSprout provides an online service that collects information about you on behalf of other third parties. ActionSprout makes this information available to the third parties that have created the campaign running on ActionSprout’s servers. This information can include any information you provide along with other personal information that we collect and that is accessible through permissions you grant to our applications on the Facebook, Twitter, and other platforms.

By completing an action you are explicitly opting in for communications from the organization who is running the action and any partners they may authorize to send correspondence to people who have opted in for communications from them.

#### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

#### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

Information that is not accessible online can be modified or deleted by sending us a request using the contact procedure in this policy. We may decline to process requests that we find are unreasonable. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

#### Changes To This Privacy Policy

This privacy policy may change from time to time. We will post any changes to the privacy policy on this page.

#### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [info@actionsprout.com](mailto:info@actionsprout.com).

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password, and Facebook UID
  * Preferences information such as action history and marketing preferences

We may also collect the following information from you:

  * Demographic information such as age, education, gender, interests, and zip code
  * Location information such as street address, city, state, and phone number

As is true of most websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to:

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Display content based upon your interests and location
  * Facilitate your transactions with other users

**Opting Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in our emails, or you can contact us by writing or email us at the address at the bottom of this page.

**Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

  * We may disclose your personal information as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, if we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so
  * We may share some of your personal information with other companies so that they can market their products or services to you. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us by writing or email us at the address below.
  * We may make your contact information available to other users that you transact with on this site to help complete transactions.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.

**Web Beacons**

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any site you visit.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet,or method of electronic storage is 100% secure, however, so we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our site, you can contact us by writing or email us at the address at the bottom of this page.

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us by writing or email us at the address below.

**How to remove your information**

You can have all of your information removed from our system by following the steps on our [removal page](https://removal.actionsprout.com/). 

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

You can contact us about this privacy policy by writing or emailing us at:

ActionSprout, INC  
1317 Commercial St, #201  
Bellingham, WA, United States 98225

Email: [info@actionsprout.com](mailto:info@actionsprout.com)
